<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SharedPreferencesFavorites</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="add_favr">Added to Favorites</string>
    <string name="remove_favr">Removed from Favorites</string>
    <string name="no_favorites_items">No Favorites</string>
    <string name="no_favorites_msg">Long press on item to add to favorites.</string>
    <string name="favorites_remove_msg">Long press on item to remove from favorites.</string>
    <string-array name="s_best">
        <item>Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don\’t matter and those who matter don\’t mind.</item>
        <item>There is never a time or place for true love. It happens accidentally, in a heartbeat, in a single flashing, throbbing moment.</item>
        <item>Love is composed of a single soul inhabiting two bodies.</item>
        <item>Never be bullied into silence. Never allow yourself to be made a victim. Accept no one\’s definition of your life; define yourself</item>
        <item>Faith is the art of holding on to things your reason has once accepted, in spite of your changing moods.</item>
        <item>We are all part of the ultimate statistic – ten out of ten die</item>
        <item>Life\’s too mysterious to take too seriously.</item>
        <item>The woman who follows the crowd will usually go no further than the crowd. The woman who walks alone is likely to find herself in places no one has been before</item>
        <item>You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else.</item>
        <item>If opportunity doesn\’t knock, build a door.</item>
        <item>You can\’t go around building a better world for people. Only people can build a better world for people. Otherwise, it\’s just a cage.</item>
        <item>Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs.</item>
        <item>It\’s not about how hard you can hit; it\’s about how hard you can get hit and keep moving forward</item>
        <item>Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears.</item>
        <item>Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect.</item>
        <item>If you want to go fast, go alone. If you want to go far, go together.</item>
        <item>Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful.</item>
        <item>Nothing in life is to be feared, it is only to be understood. Now is the time to understand more so that we may fear less.</item>
        <item>The mind is everything. what you think you become.</item>
        <item>Close your eyes and I\’ll Kiss you.</item>
        <item>I must destroy you with hugs and kisses</item>
        <item>Close your eyes and I\’ll Kiss you.</item>
        <item>Do not take life too seriously. You will never get out of it alive</item>
        <item>A daily selfie reminds you what you look for.</item>
        <item>Have a seat, we were expecting you.</item>
        <item>Keep smiling because life is a beautiful thing and there\’s so much to smile about.</item>
        <item>Sometimes life can surprise you with a happy coincidence</item>
        <item>What if I told you, you can eat without posting it on Instagram.</item>
        <item>Warning – You might fall in love with me.</item>
        <item>Takes 2 selfies. Deletes 22 selfies</item>
        <item>Don\’t copy my style of taking Selfies</item>
        <item>Be the girl with not just beauty, but also swag</item>
        <item>When I feel a little down, I put on my favorite high heels and dance.</item>
        <item>Everyone said I could be Anything. So I became Sexy!</item>
        <item>A girl should be 2 things, classy and fabulous</item>
        <item>Genius by birth. Evil by choice.</item>
        <item>I am not one in a million kind of girl I am once in a lifetime kind of woman.</item>
        <item>Silly girls are the best.</item>
        <item>Proof that I can do selfies better than you.</item>
        <item>I know I\’m lucky that I\’m so cute.</item>
        <item>Some days start better than others.</item>
        <item>Truth is, I\’m crazy for you. And everyone can see that but you.</item>
        <item>Sometimes life can surprise you with a happy coincidence</item>
        <item>I decide the vibe.</item>
        <item>If we could only turn back time…</item>
        <item>Keep smiling because life is a beautiful thing and there\’s so much to smile about.</item>
        <item>No one is you. That\’s your power!</item>
        <item>When your mom lectures you about how you need to lose weight for an hour and your\’re like \’shit i don\’t care I have got a skinny mirror to make me look good\’!</item>
        <item>This is to the Echos of our laughter. The looks That we Share. The never ending gossips.</item>
        <item>Life isn\’t perfect..But my Hair is! #selfieaddict</item>
        <item>I woke up like this.</item>
        <item>One does not simply “Let it go”.</item>
        <item>Is Google a boy or a girl? Obviously a girl because it won\’t let you finish your sentence without suggesting other ideas.</item>
        <item>It\’s so beautiful when a boy smiles.</item>
        <item>Don\’t be like the rest of them, darling.</item>
        <item>Life isn\’t perfect..But my Hair is!</item>
        <item>Always classy, never trashy, and a little bit sassy.</item>
        <item>Got my coffee and donut.</item>
        <item>If I like my art why should it be anyone else\’s decision how “good” or “bad” it is. Art shouldn\’t have a grade. If I\’m proud of it and what I accomplished why should anyone else tell me it isn\’t good enough?</item>
        <item>Watch more sunsets than netflix.</item>
        <item>Hey, I just met you, this is crazy.</item>
        <item>At least this balloon is attracted to me!</item>
        <item>I must destroy you with hugs and kisses</item>
        <item>Stop looking for happiness in the same place you just lost it.</item>
        <item>Girl, I have to call you back.</item>
        <item>Have a seat, we were expecting you.</item>
        <item>I\’ve finally counted.</item>
        <item>Proof that I can do selfies better than you.</item>
        <item>Escape the ordinary.</item>
        <item>Sweeter than honey.</item>
        <item>OMG that\’s so cute.</item>
        <item>A friend will always make you Smile, specially when you don\’t want to…</item>
        <item>Life is like a balloon..If you never let go, you will not know how high can you rise.</item>
        <item>Sometimes life can surprise you with a happy coincidence.</item>
        <item>You can\’t afford my Swag Bitch! #selfie</item>
        <item>A Caffeine subordinate living thing</item>
        <item>A human. Being.</item>
        <item>A man of puzzle and force, whose force is surpassed just by his secret</item>
        <item>Completely clumsy, proudest of geek n nerd, decreaser of world sucking</item>
        <item>Forcefully early stages and stuff</item>
        <item>All you fashionable people need to quit wearing Nirvana shirts on the off chance that you don\’t even hear them out.</item>
        <item>Simple during childbirth, computerized by configuration</item>
        <item>Anybody knows my Instagram username not making another record once more.</item>
        <item>Are you a broker on the grounds that I\\’d like you to leave me a credit</item>
        <item>Uncovered. Frequently Unreliable. Effectively distract</item>
        <item>Conceived at an exceptionally youthful age</item>
        <item>Amigo, would you be able to standard?</item>
        <item>Light, waggish, effectual, inexhaustible, demiurgic, friendly advertising buddy, independent thousandaire Outdoors is plans</item>
        <item>Would someone be able to let me know my Instagram username I bolted myself out and I don\’t realize what to do</item>
        <item>Chocolate doesn\’t make inquiries, chocolate gets it</item>
        <item>Espresso Drinker, eReader Addict, Blogger. I\’m exceptionally occupied and wonderful</item>
        <item>Currently featuring in my own particular reality show titled, A Modern Cinderella; One Girl\’s Search for Love and Shoes</item>
        <item>Try not to think for a brief moment that I really mind what you need to say</item>
        <item>Think ambitiously (little textual style)</item>
        <item>Eating an entire apple center on the grounds that you can\’t be tried setting off to the canister, let it out, you\’ve done it.</item>
        <item>Each tempest comes up short on downpour</item>
        <item>Remarkable finishes in "us" fortuitous event? I think not</item>
        <item>By and large, the easy way out appeals. Additionally, I am fantastic at parallel stopping.</item>
        <item>God favor this chaotic situation</item>
        <item>Great Samaritan, cleaned up competitor, particularly skilled napper.</item>
        <item>Have heaps of hair and like appalling things</item>
        <item>Here to serve. the feline overlord</item>
        <item>I completely loathe Instagram, and whatever else needing to do with hashtags.</item>
        <item>I generally feel dismal for seedless watermelons, in light of the fact that imagine a scenario in which they needed children.</item>
        <item>I am an on-screen character and an essayist and I co-made my breakfast and my child, Malachai.</item>
        <item>I am returning to face the truth that an ordinary day is not lager on the shoreline or calamari in the tummy.</item>
        <item>I can quote (Insert motion picture) superior to anything you and every one of your companions.</item>
        <item>I Can\’t recollect who I stole my bio from or why</item>
        <item>I have not lost my psyche its went down on HD some place.</item>
        <item>I have this new hypothesis that human immaturity doesn\’t end until your mid thirties.</item>
        <item>I trust one day I adore something the route ladies in advertisements love yogurt</item>
        <item>I took a gander at my Instagram photographs and acknowledged I look excellent.</item>
        <item>I once wheezed a beanie weenie through my nose. I likewise made a stallion black out in Costa Rica.</item>
        <item>I just rap caucasionally</item>
        <item>I lean toward my plays on words expected</item>
        <item>I put the hot in maniacal</item>
        <item>I as of late surrendered Warcraft so my efficiency, and drinking, have expanded drastically.</item>
        <item>I shouldn\’t be permitted to go on Snapchat, Facebook or Instagram when I\’m intoxicated!</item>
        <item>Despite everything I don\’t comprehend Twitter, yet here I am.</item>
        <item>I talk like a child and I never pay for beverages.</item>
        <item>I believe its irregular if a young lady doesn\’t have an Instagram now days.</item>
        <item>I used to act. I additionally hip twirl and eat Jolly Ranchers not generally in the meantime however.</item>
        <item>Smile A little more, Regret A little less.</item>
        <item>Be like Snow, Cold but beautiful.</item>
        <item>Because when you stop and look around, This life is pretty amazing.</item>
        <item>Go wild, for a while</item>
        <item>I\’M on a new level</item>
        <item>she\’s a queen with a little bit of savage</item>
        <item>Beauty attracts the eye but personality captures the heart</item>
        <item>You only live once, but if you do it right, one is enough</item>
        <item>May your clothes be comfy, your coffee be strong, and your Monday be short</item>
        <item>Always find time for the things that make you feel happy to be alive</item>
        <item>Be happy for this moment, This moment is your life.</item>
        <item>Great things never came from comfort zones.Surround yourself with people who get it.</item>
        <item>Never sacrifice three things: Your family, your heart, or your dignity.</item>
        <item>Be the energy you want to attract.</item>
        <item>I\’m too busy working on my grass to notice if yours is greener</item>
        <item>I distance myself from people for a reason</item>
        <item>Dress like you\’re already famous</item>
        <item>Let\’s do what we love and do a lot of it.</item>
        <item>Work hard,s o you can shop harder</item>
        <item>Some days, I wish could go back in life, not to change things, just to feel a few things twice.</item>
        <item>Don\’t ever let anyone dull your sparkle.</item>
        <item>Wake up it;s time to dominate your workout.</item>
        <item>First I drink coffee.Then I do the things</item>
        <item>Keep your eyes o the stars, and your feet on the ground.</item>
        <item>Happy mind, happy life.</item>
        <item>See good in all things.</item>
        <item>Life was meant for good friends and great adventures.</item>
        <item>The trouble is, you think you have a time.</item>
        <item>Good things take time.</item>
        <item>Never underestimate the power of a good outfit on a bad day.</item>
        <item>Memories take us back, Dreams take us forward.</item>
        <item>There are so many beautiful reasons to be happy.</item>
        <item>I\’m not searching for my other half because I \’m not a half.</item>
        <item>Good friends are hard to find, harder to leave, and impossible to forget.</item>
        <item>Don;t fcuk with my feelings, just because you\’re unsure of your own.</item>
        <item>You are like the ocean, pretty enough on the surface, but dive down into your depths, you\’ll find beauty</item>
        <item>most. people never see.</item>
        <item>Cause I may be bad but I\’m perfectly good at it.</item>
        <item>See the good.</item>
        <item>Friends may change, but the memories last forever.</item>
        <item>And so the adventure begins</item>
        <item>Just remember that negative people usually have negative bank accounts to match.</item>
        <item>Enjoy the little things.</item>
        <item>Live the life that people write novels about.</item>
        <item>Make people feel Good about themselves.</item>
        <item>Strive for progress, not perfection.</item>
        <item>You look like something I drew with my hand.</item>
        <item>Oh, you\’re a model?What\’s your agency, Instagram?</item>
        <item>I need a six month holiday, twice a year.</item>
        <item>I just don\’t want to look back and think “I could\’ve eaten something.</item>
        <item>Behind every girl\’s selfie is approximately 39, nearly identical photos, that just didn\’t make the cut.</item>
        <item>If I was funny, I would have a good Instagram captions.</item>
        <item>I had fun once, it was horrible.</item>
        <item>Invite me to play candy crush one more time.</item>
        <item>Girls be like no makeup!</item>
        <item>Real men don\’t take selfies.</item>
        <item>I know I\’m lucky that I\’m so cute.</item>
        <item>I think you are lacking vitamin me!</item>
        <item>Onions make me sad. A lot of people don\’t realize it.</item>
        <item>When you\’re downie eat a brownie</item>
        <item>I don\’t even believe myself when I say I\’ll be ready in 5vminutes</item>
        <item>I\’m on a seafood diet.I see food and.I eat it.</item>
        <item>I\’m not saying I hate you, you are literally that Monday of my life.</item>
        <item>A blind man walks into a bar…and a chair..and a table.</item>
        <item>I didn\’t choose the thug life, the thug life chose me.</item>
        <item>So apparently you are a player, Nice to meet you. I\’m the coach.</item>
        <item>Weekend, please don\’t leave me.</item>
        <item>I\’ll never try to fit in.I was born to STAND OUT.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>